smart-ip.net 2018-12-22

# Privacy Policy

This document describes a policy of collecting and usage of your private information on a Smart-IP.net website. By using our website means you are completely agree and consent with the current policies. If you are not, please, do not use this website, clean-up your cookies belongs to this web site and close your browser.

## 1\. Collecting the Information

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, using the tools or subscribe to our newsletters.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or other contact and personal information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

## 2\. Privacy Information Usage

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * **To personalize your experience**  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs 
  * **To improve our website**  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you 
  * **To process transactions**  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 
  * **To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature**
  * **To send periodic emails**  
The email address you provide for your request processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your request.

## 3\. Privacy Information Protection

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

## 4\. Cookies

Yes, we are using cookies (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

## 5\. Disclosing an Information to 3d Parties

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## 6\. Third Party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## 7\. Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## 8\. Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms Of Use section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

## 9\. Your Consent

By using our site, you lawful consent to our web site privacy policy and our Terms Of Use of this web site.

## 10\. Changes to Our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

Last modified: Dec 2, 2011 10:11:03 PM
